Andrea Gamez

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/andrea-gamez-b228901a9

GitHub: https://github.com/AndreG303

Portfolio:https://andreg303.github.io/dreami-react-portfolio/

San Diego, CA (973) 767-3359 andreamgamez@gmail.com

WHOIAM

I am a Full Stack Web Developer - determined and hard working with a passion for creative solutions. Knowledgeable in, testing, and debugging processes. Bringing forth proficiency in concept, design, installation, testing and maintenance of web systems.

WHAT SETS ME APART

I have a broad background in management and with experience training and leading teams. By leveraging my educational background in psychology and fashion I find creative solutions to big picture problems. Recently in coding bootcamp I landed the lead project manager role on the three major projects and graduated with two recognition awards: most likely to win a design award and most likely to inspire future generations.

EXPERIENCE

Trademark 5150, San Diego,CA — *Intern*

IUNE 2020 - PRESENT

Work closely with the development team, as well as the design team to assist in updating and editing content, development of coding and designing the layout and functionality according to the client's specifications.

Kensington Furniture, Northfield,NJ — Social Media specialist, Showroom Stylist

JUNE 2016 - MAY 2017

Collaborated with Digital Marketer creating ideas for PR events, social media platforms and website (videos, photo shoots, posts,blogs). Revamped and created 100% of the floor plan and merchandising.

Bloomingdale's, Hackensack, NJ — Lead merchandiser

DECEMBER 2012 - DECEMBER 2015

Perform managerial functions in the absence of the Merchandise Manager.

Trained and mentored a group of 10 associates to help them achieve their maximum potential. "Golden B" Award Winner. "Rookie of the Year" Award Winner.

EDUCATION

Rutgers University, New Brunswick, NJ — Full Stack Web Development.

Fashion Institute of Technology, NY, NY — Fashion Stylist

Universidad El Bosque, Bogotá, Colombia — *Psychology degree*

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML5
CSS3
Bootstrap
JavaScript
jQuery
Web APIs
Node.JS
Express
MySQL
NoSQL
MongoDB
React

PROJECTS

Media-Made

React, Mongodb, Axios

https://github.com/AndreG3 03/MEDIA-MADE

https://damp-ocean-72048. herokuapp.com/

Stellar Sonic

HTML, CSS, JS, MYSQL

https://github.com/AndreG3 03/Stellar-Sonic

https://dry-shelf-60979.her okuapp.com/

Virtual Art Gallery

HTML, CSS, JQUERY

https://github.com/AndreG3 03/Virtual_Art_Gallery

https://nlamonaco86.github.i o/Virtual_Art_Gallery/

I am Bilingual

English/Spanish